I've got all the over the region being in the biosecdenial group and they did it in my team, going cold.
Again, look, I'm scared of the personal preferences.
We have one.
Patrick Clark.
That's right.
What do you think?
Yes.
With the college answer for this morning, I got that.
It's my innocent.
But the 20 of that, I think, is that it's not for X.
It's going to be serious, in fact.
Okay.
Five people in the ages.
Also, what do we go about?
Up and down that street for people in front of that.
What can we find an all the way?
Do you know it's 59?
Can we find truck right?
Or have people talk about, through there, or other words?
Whether it's, like, mot, trucks.
Big number.
Half of the people?
You can't even have to record that.
You guys don't exactly.
They're not going to do that.
So I go to say, we're going to answer some of the issues there.
If anybody's interested in something I don't like to see you do, it's also a different
bridge debate either.
We're going to be trying to get as far as correct back to people.
We're going to be able to grab a link or another group of drugs.
So I don't like that.
People are going to be trying to tell us from each group to each group.
That's true.
That's really rare.
And we really, really want to try to work out.
The idea is that I think that it's some of the on-premise street
that people are sort of stops like that.
Because we can't not be still in the right track.
All we have to do is because they're busy and stops.
So like I said, people, they don't like to kind of say this.
But once I do not know what I'm going to say,
and there's something that I'd be able to kind of show you about,
if you know, for a couple of years, no stops and ends and ends and ends and ends and ends and ends and ends and ends and ends.
So I can say this is going to be dangerous for the kids to put it up there.
And the people who live here trying to get in the car,
they're not going to get in the car.
So if there's somebody who's sitting in the car,
One of the most beautiful patients, they're going to get in the car.
They're not going to get in the car.
But I don't appreciate time.
So take it.
We can use it.
For three, consent and gender.
So we have to bring me into the group.
I support the babies.
I can't repeat that for a long time.
I can't deny that it can't remove your meaning next week,
but support organizations for the lives on that day and the so that we can move
from next week.
We'll move on on my left.
The session right now, though,
I'll go downstairs and see if you can share this with me.
I can really, yeah.
You can guess you were allowed to buy it.
It's quicker than me.
I'll have that.
So I appreciate you getting the time to address everybody here.
Those are the moment you had some see the testing.
There's your new commissioner for all the candidates.
And I'm coming tonight.
I'm going to talk about this at our board meeting.
So the kind of was the full room in the back of the county
in the session.
Did you tonight?
If you tell this to your opportunity,
then some of the things that we need to probably be working together.
On the good market meeting in turn,
so I think that's what we would like to talk about.
The new one thing we have to talk about is those of us that are elected officials.
The new one, I have a long report for both of us.
It's a safety and security of our community.
Do you agree with that?
The problem is, no one really talks about one or two years.
So I've got 1250 papers of the county commission.
No one ever talks about one or two years.
Somebody can identify what the elected official number two
which wants to go to is.
I'll be glad to have that in options.
You've listened to this.
To me, it's a very long report.
And you need the vote.
You know, we have security, people's community security.
But we also have to make sure our community members
can take care of the needs of our community.
But that doesn't necessarily mean the police.
I don't know.
I mean, the number two thought we don't belong to the local state of the country.
But the community has a whole without a economic development.
It might be a priority to be in the morning economy.
Without it, there is a priority.
We lose everything and lose opportunities.
And your return is you're not moving forward to backing up.
Well, I believe that's right.
We are, as a county, likely to be right now today.
And I'm going to simply think why.
What we call it.
I mean, no disrespect.
What about the sweet about here?
Because there are some great things going on in the community.
I am included.
The other towns.
But we need to want closer, collectively, to get things going on.
First, it's this weekend.
The event at the cold.
And what we've done was here, from all reports,
since the great successful event, just that the event
alone brought the improved trucks,
I hear a little bit of regard to pop that there too,
the streets were full, people were meant to have.
The folks there were colon decided to kind of butt
and train with the day to night, right?
They did the hard work to keep moving forward,
instead of being segmented back and back.
And what was the result of that?
Meaning, if you were to put in, was it a success?
That's how you're only continuing the development.
The folks at the colon, the side of it,
during it, global life, can't end it.
They might say that, but they're moving forward.
While cities and panelists in are state
and across this country, we're even entering the flow
at their events.
I think it's so we ought to be proud of it.
But my and the people that are colon decided not
to just say that, it's a great success,
but it's something we need to have, and we need to go on.
And it shows the life, like, great city of our community,
that they are willing to come out, and support our community
and our economic development needs it.
As well as the officials, let's show them a little bit there.
Well, I'd like to just talk about some historic opportunities
that we have right now, every city, town,
and county in the US are about to receive funds
to the very, where we're coming at.
As a county, we're looking to receive about $6 million
in recovery at lunch.
The city itself, city of Miami, is looking to receive
about 2.1 million in recovery at lunch.
Now, before we all spend the tax, remember,
especially the old lives of pay days in what the government
has put in the red table, truly not fine to those
of housing in that land.
They get a couple of very broad ideas, no broadband,
this type of thing.
The reality is there is multiple, multiple counties in the state
as well as tons of cities in the entire town.
That aren't going to be able to do anything.
Because they won't qualify.
For instance, the city of Miami can put in 2.1 million
on a broadband load, that means coming to the city.
The county, that we have the broadband out there,
to become a part of it, and that's it, million bucks.
The put in the red broadband.
It's tough for the regular, isn't it, a million bucks.
But they again have millions out there for us, too.
The very, very few of us in that county, the moment off the period,
we have to collectively work together.
Because there are times of the charity
in the way that we're doing the county.
That won't be able to hit that side.
but there's a collective group, it's a county, we can all move forward as opposed to the overall community.
On top of that, we all know about the $2 trillion infrastructure building that, right, that's been passed.
Out of that, $2 trillion, that's being put out.
If you guys realize what's happening right now, what's interesting to you.
We're already behind everyone, what's in this group is already behind the government.
And here's what happens, this is why it has to come to street media to let go of the buildings.
Currently in Washington, DC, 290, there's a small public agency of county town cities in the DC,
pitching their ideas for mass supply and creating the public zones.
For the federal rights of the city, it has to be important.
Right now, we don't have any plans right now.
This area, in DC, or towards federal quarters in our federal offices, on what are mass supply and stuff.
I haven't seen my hands.
I don't mean to have I seen all the counties in mass supply and right now, but we need $2 trillion here.
We have to wet together slightly to get this from the floor.
Okay?
That money is destroyed.
There are cities in all the hiring volumes.
For hiring volumes, it's in the LHAC to get this money.
Because, again, the red tape, and the information is put out by the federal government in the sole base.
And, or we're seeing what this administration has done.
These are the bottom of the federal case.
So they're looking for it.
Can't wet.
But we are behind the curve today.
We're behind it.
We have to catch it.
No matter where you stand on that, when you feel it's dead,
and you can never take that, or it's a new deal.
The money is there.
It's money.
We need to take it down and put it to your use for our community.
We need to have this a TV partners that can help us, lobby that community, and get that money in our community.
We need to work together as a slightly improved to think of bigger, more or more mass replants.
And do stuff this like the coal in the internet.
So I'm not going to stick with this hat.
Well, we're going to keep moving this land forward.
We'll need to do that right now.
We're behind it.
You know, as the distance bank is a getting the 200 million plus stimulus that we can get here for infrastructure is what?
What's the distance bank to get that?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I can't find the distance bank.
We need that money.
And with your help, I think we don't want to lose it.
As a carryover, we need that all of our curve, the own projects.
And it's one of the other properties to apply gold.
To get ready to design my gear.
One problem that we don't want to be able to be able to be able to be able to be a citizen.
We're looking at opportunities there, some of that will want you to see on some of the audience.
We're also looking at other alternative ideas to get that whole facility that will be
a property up and moving in for generations to come in.
We're also looking at other properties that the county owns, but getting out into an economic development,
zone with sorts of speed that we could designate ourselves to start running it in,
and getting more track-it-door opportunities for them to be a good decision.
And at the same time, we need to get the same environment and the others around us,
commerce, all all, lying on, fairly.
To join in on this and have this iconic vibe by the high building corridor.
We're already heard of the long-awaited zone of the community,
to get the high building of the building.
There have been a lot of discussions on becoming sister cities with families
in the region of Toronto, such as Chicago.
We believe that.
And had that conversation this yesterday.
How does that work?
Here's the thing.
Let's say we can bring in the main factors here that makes the screw thread for a level,
but Chicago has the last manufacturing line.
We put together one of those systems,
Chicago and other properties are viewed in this building,
for very much to actually be really looking for economic partners out here in the middle of the west.
We need to be a part of what some of these folks in T-Monkey systems
with that.
They are always doing millions of dollars in order to call you in our community,
to get these things moving forward.
There are studies being picked up right now by our two community partners.
These are people showing the role-playing in the ones that you go with $65,000 right now,
for a feasibility study of commercial retail,
opportunities right around the county.
These give us all a lot of what some should benefit for.
Our main partners as well have been able to continue these before the end of our communities,
and they want the partner of us to move to the county for.
We must engage in support areas for the end of our new pollackings.
So those are the only only pretty good times.
And the downside and the reason one of this can be done is to move us to the light of the decisions of the suicide.
We felt that this happened to have a lot of the doctorate.
The only people we have in our lives is that the public put us in power.
They put us in leadership to take this community forward.
We must act on it.
I know I'm not going to put the task.
I'm sure you guys have heard from the task.
You know, one thing that you have to stop doing, you know what the county,
especially in our cultural areas is...
stop getting stuck in it. We have litigation and don't go in for a second in decades. We have
areas that are not being developed in the student life doubt. If you have a good rich,
we have to get ahead of that further. Are you still here for a problem in your own? Good problem
in one time. Good flood a little bit. It's highly of litigation for a long time. These type of
bowl acts in the community of the United Kingdom and out of the head of the litigation. I'm just
now that problem is going to back in the fall for us to be able to do the development of these
properties and also sell that to somebody else at what's to take matters. Right now they're
getting sold because they're tired of it. So we need to get old and get this stuff done. We can't
know that that needs going without the places and the jobs that have been launched. Little little
great deal is that we've got going back and continue to build that one to sit in the fall. We can only
be caught up in years and years and years of doing the same old single. It's exactly the new results.
I believe that truth is the death of the student we said. We have to find the officials,
the bus look at ourselves from the site. If we're ready to move forward or we're going back that,
the people who trusted us to lead and do the hard work. That's why I'm here today. I can hear you saying
how do you do this? That's not part of it. How do you do this? So I'm asking you the same title,
the point, what are two members of your caption, who work with me as a accountant, to come up with
some ideas, because again, this money is already involved. I'm not talking about that individual. We're
coming back. I'm going to talk about the efforts to understand that. I'm going to be truly true to me. And
I, on this, don't speak. I would like to make sense to the newly elected Mr. Trevor, and to reset,
is the newly appointed way. People's members of what are both academic work here, kind of,
of their problems. So I feel that one of those general, both of those general, we made the point,
because they got fresh ice, fresh ideas, processed set out of what some of the stuff. But I'm asking
for the caption, the point where those are also together to work on this little small community,
for some other leadership community. And I think that, that we're going to continue to close with this,
we'll tell you the worst. It's going to be talking about all this when we, when we've added some
folks to the Washington DC. I'll tell you the worst story that all of you can tell me right about this chapter.
I'm going to have the privilege of understanding the misery of what these five military classes have
been, I'm sorry, the future goes going to the classes of the New Year's and New Year's and New Year's,
and I ask them a simple question. Raise your hand. If you're planning on going to college or
still straight school, I'm going to ask them.
all the four raise your hand on the four, okay?
Then I said, leave your hand as well.
It is, after you graduate college with school church school,
you can come back for community,
and let your biggest home, less than 9% of their hands up.
Well, if our own generation is even willing to give us a shot,
word drug folks.
So I think in that way, right now, it's across all schools.
And the Congress is out of it, and the fought falls out of it.
And the numbers in my hand, the five to seven people,
the numbers for preacher, over 75% of our community,
teacher, it's planning on not staying.
When I asked them why, you also know that one reason was,
you take it in your jobs, right?
They said, there's no other reason.
They said, it's not a job.
They said, you got two people living here.
They don't want to see if I have a place.
That's a whole story.
And those that were before us in these seats, in these offices,
they did the best they did.
From a partner to set forward, take it to the meaningful,
and then hold that everybody here in the stands,
can't do a door for it, and hold it work with you all,
from the city's standpoint.
And we should do it together, collectively,
or stronger together.
Bringing in rights to keep partners, to help us,
giving community people involved, bringing in right-name
factors, private investment, private equity,
giving their basic business.
So taking all of us, what they call that is,
that's what they want us to take first steps.
All of those things are counted.
The board kind of commissioners will take it with you,
and I hope you'll join us in inside.
Thank you.
Questions?
Let's start with one of the work we did on that last year.
First, you might not want to make a third.
We'll make a couple of other people also.
This problem will be the fact that I made a third.
They give us a third.
You might have it.
We'll also have a talk about it, and figure out
what we want to do there.
Does anybody have any questions to see?
Okay, anyone?
I think it's a good stop.
But the problem is that we're doing it here.
And I would say that from me, I agree with all the third news.
And I think you're, you're, you're a spot-on with our students.
I've heard the same thing.
Well, that's not good.
And this is kind of the platform.
You don't have to go through anymore.
And this is the big opportunity for us to,
and again, it makes me very well.
But I think it's something that we've problems with need.
Like, you did it in part together.
Same old gas.
You did it in part together.
Thank you.
Well, I think we've got to be honest with you.
This is where we now have got to keep your tables,
and in the, with the chair of the nation.
We're easy to disqualize.
This is a game.
And we can't have any questions from our agenda.
And it's not a second.
We need to be a piece of the way.
We're going to have a bit of time.
We're still with our law enforcement issues that we have.
We sent it down to the British side of the river,
which is the man who made the chair of the nation,
under the birth decision, which is in turn,
and continue to be in the various evasion in Oklahoma.
The chief, at least in the hiding position, chief,
attended four court hearings.
Today, all in the dirt position.
Yeah.
It's obviously spreading to this side of the river.
The legal process.
The law mind is this is a,
the quickest and easiest way to get our law enforcement officers.
The ability to deal with crimes that may be committed.
By any means for against the against,
on the other side of the river.
And it's something that needs to be done.
It's possible.
That's why we're bringing it to you and under the agenda.
I think it is.
Okay.
Questions about it.
The chief, or I would like to try to introduce.
I'm not going to ask this another permanent solution,
but it's something that sort of serves as a soft air.
I'm sure I should personally,
I'm not going to switch.
But basically, because across the entire,
we're not going to be softer than the journey.
Right.
And hopefully we will be having similar agreements with other crimes
that will roll out in the hands of the young,
as a very good regime.
Hi, all right.
I'll go ahead and put some and then I'll put some further.
Number 10 but I'll take action.
What's the question?
My question?
I'm very nervous.
Pardon, I'll harassment.
Thank you.
Okay, please go ahead.
Thank you very much.
I'm very nervous.
Thank you.
We're getting on for any extra.
For any manner, absolute community residents and developments.
So, I have a few.
So, I have a great answer.
So, I'm not going to the concert.
I'll be meeting you to have a little bit of a welcoming event.
I have to do that.
I want to go, I went figuring out how to be bored.
That's not what I can talk about.
So, she did a really good job.
I had a life to talk.
There's so many things there to me in the out.
Some of them laughing, Jerry.
There's a pleasure to side.
But even more than that, just to see our stationary pack,
to see everybody in that on this floor is going to go in.
I'm going to see a lot of the part across the street being utilized.
But there are a few drugs in the very wrong.
The amount of animal acts, that amount of that weight, that amount.
So, that answer, put people in our restaurants, in our gas stations.
And build up our community.
I know there was, that leads to great people that flew into California for this doctor.
One of the things in the floor that I love for sure.
Sometimes, I always say that out of us, that we're sitting there.
I think there's a lot of other people there.
The bank officer.
I know those who resist or change them.
They don't even know what to sit here.
They have a life.
So, it was something to build up in my eyes.
And what we need to continue to do.
And that is to continue to bring things in the clothing.
Just like that.
And you can feel that they've got the communities to bring people in.
Just put their knowledge on outside of it.
And those outside of all of them are extremely important.
And the ganglons track those dollars on track.
So, you know, they're here.
And jurism is huge.
And they see it all over the place.
But right back.
With us being willing to do step out of the county's concert.
You know, the one thing that I'm going to say during that concert was,
she parked her bus, March 14th.
We're going to go.
We're going to go to 97 days before she got back.
We're going to cross a day in Montau, Montau, Montau.
And she was attacked.
And I've been able to play.
Because they didn't be able to go on again.
So, I think the concert heard a little bit of depression.
Thank you.
And I said, they got the filming, but she's used it.
But on that line, it was the first stop.
Because it was really good for our community to have it here.
So hopefully, in any joke with this group,
the power of standing up is going to be here.
It's that good.
It's going to be a great, great, great job.
And I call it the answer to everything.
It's going to be a good job.
You did a much opportunity to understand it,
because yeah, really a fine, I just
would love that moment to really do it.
And the fact that we had a craft deal there,
which taught people how to do that.
And I'm going to have to do that, but myself
is a little bit like a watch.
Everything that plays with it all in is so that we really
utilize more than what we acted.
Secondly, is a little bit more of us.
Our chief police is here, a little bit of a great job.
Also, Nico, our team, I got one of the last people,
so I'm going to have all this stuff, so a great job for our police
officer to the team, not about a part of the team.
He made this bust, you know, you need to take it out,
as I say, we're saying more of this officer,
because they have it with him.
So we appreciate that.
Well, I've made it here for that.
They've got to know you're last week.
And it's just a late third year in our obligations,
it's just a little bit of a year.
So I want to thank the committee for our service,
but I can be in the, you know, we also up here
and staffs are going to be there.
And we do it as long as it is.
And then on the years, you've been going to have to wait here.
So that's five, two years, you've gone there,
and I'm going to sort of want to be in the,
and it's important to me, thank you for that.
She's now, you can hang on with it.
And she's going to go to the, thank you, thank you very much.
I want to make sure we thank the committee for our service,
right, thank you, thank you.
But I'm sitting right in the middle of the day,
I'm very happy to get there.
OK, so we'll do this right on the other side.
Here we go.
We'll make it short, please.
OK, OK.
Hey, last night, you didn't see nine of the days.
I mean, you saw that.
We had to do restaurants, towns,
actually, they brought that, they didn't even need me.
They were able to walk, and so when we see nine of the days,
they came out of the store, and those two restaurants,
wow, there were swamps of the crazy.
And that is, that's all that you can't pay for.
I mean, you can never pay for this, right?
I have to buy it, or I can even, and so today, there's
And I made a close up, I recorded this on the TV and I made a close last night.
And we've been just about 24 hours.
And we didn't end this week.
We didn't end the 9,000 to 15 hours.
I know that both the dog house and the exact that they were seeing
the phone call, since it ran last night.
And I continued today.
And they did the phone call, so people don't even be able
from all in the United States.
I'll squarely, new people.
I mean, DNA, I think, they've been both awesome.
And they're all, I think, too, but I saw some of those,
they're all recovering.
It's actually sort of a new role.
But it's not about veterans.
It's our veterans in the union.
And it didn't have to, they're right in the heart rate.
Thank you.
The end of the show is our community.
Our protection.
So great things are happening here.
People know some, I don't know what we're noticing.
And we just got to take that and run with it.
We've got to continue to do the things really.
People know some good things are happening.
And the community, we're doing it together.
And that's the best part.
So it's not one person who's doing it all around.
It's a community set it up and doing it together.
And that goes back to what Steve said.
As far as they go on with all the heart, you need to drop them.
They're all the way to the work that we do as we get them.
And so I think they take that and I'm excited about it.
Be sure of that.
Anyway, I'll tell you later.
I'll tell you later.
All right.
I think my parents have never done that.
I've got a couple of them.
They should be sure.
Of course, they're all cool.
It's something that everybody's been waiting for.
They're being in the liner.
That's been going in.
So the old liner is now going to be bleeding through the pool.
And they've been working on the covering around the curvy.
The preparation for the new liner.
The filter repair will also be in this week.
And always remember that the portion of time in this project is completely blind.
The evening night is a great curve.
There's going to be a selection of the liner.
They will get a top number to try out.
So in the evening, you said they were going to look down.
They're going to have to run along.
And so we'll have to come down to the summer.
I'll go back.
The question.
We're about to start.
We're going to do it.
I think people might have to do that.
We're going to.
We're going to be there.
So we're going to have to do this.
Tico, Tico Park, the shakes structure,
you know what I'm saying here, nine people up,
being in the concrete door,
being placed in this week, again,
this project, this complete space one, this project,
that comes part of 100 of this space,
just by the, from the cell of the woods.
So we've done about it.
Total project and all the upgrades
in the middle of the years,
and I'm sure we've done about 100 of this working on the shop.
And we've got some food for that.
So kids going on a lovely,
and of course, are our corporate board,
we're not sure if we can do that kind of that.
The other way to the shop,
is to shop, click, and mine,
share your hand and make it first.
It's from 10 to 2.
We've got shops, we've got a lot of silver shops.
We've got nice neat tags.
We've got a lot of microjigs.
And five dollar jigs.
This is a great opportunity for our families.
Let me confess to my ancient challenges.
The best.
It's a great opportunity to gather,
it's a great thing to learn.
The range.
So big thanks to the community,
and the community, and the community.
We're looking to the end of the course.
The need.
So as part of our community,
we go to the chat,
and they can first learn a lot of discussion
with the online professionals and consultants.
We're looking at this as our digital readers.
Since we've been able to,
the cycle of one of the readings,
that's the southeast, and so, of course,
you can work these in a piece of our free.
The total amount of 3,000,
one or very one,
the 99, 24,000,
which actually is great.
So that's where you are.
They're actually going to get rid of the readings,
because you're all about challenging that kind of thing.
For everything,
we're going to get into the readings.
In the end,
the one that comes up,
starts now in the year three.
One that has an issue,
with the meter,
and the question,
and I have absolutely lots of here.
The number of 98,
five or two, six,
three, five, four.
And we have the addition,
and the addition,
and the addition, and the addition.
That being said,
we have the time,
and we're going to give this enough paper,
and the trees.
So the next tree,
and the number of the year, yeah?
So, of course,
we'll start out with mainstream.
And so,
we talked to the modules today,
a couple of times,
they actually start showing up on the side.
They will be in later,
honestly,
to start building on.
Sometimes,
but, so, there's some area there.
And that is between 34,
so, they're going to come in and build all that off.
And they're also going to,
they're just a couple of spots.
Between,
second and third,
they're also going to move
the bad asphalt,
and probably do it.
We got something that, and then, actually, we, like, this, we, whatever, meaning it goes that I'm
fooled.
So then, and then, actually, they're all busy coming in and asked for everything.
So they won't file, but they don't want anything, and he gives it, it'll be nice.
So then we can start working on getting the chatter, take a look at what they need, everything else.
How are all there to the, he doesn't have options that the girl will be looking for, they'll be
going to be kind of a bit tired, and then we're going to be able to have it as any question,
but I'm making sure you do that in the question.
So, they started it, it's going to be a question that I, I, the problem of the thing that I'm
going to, whatever, meaning it.
The first thing, right now.
So, we have it back in the morning.
I know it's hard, because it's starting to come in.
When you said boxes, you're referring to the ones that are just, you mean, installed it.
Yeah, that.
The electric, look at that observation means you must be in the lamps.
Well, there's, there's no lamp, but that is for, that is for the large use of two hundred.
So, the lamp is called by twenty-two.
Yeah, there's like twenty-two, you should, you know.
But when you go down that, I always make it in the mirror.
So, when I get down that, for they go on, I have to do what they want.
That's what they do.
You should bounce out.
Yeah.
We got to look at it.
And then also, of course, think that's what it was.
Up here in the pond, whole pane into the lower treks.
That little area, that's being taken care of, right?
Yes.
That's what, we have a meeting with Oda and we discuss that because it's kind of weird how Oda does
and I think it's that it's that he's never really maintain it.
But here you go.
I mean, whoa, we'll make sure he's taken care of it.
Because I actually really bad and thought that it was a follow-up.
Yeah.
So, all right, we're going to do the same thing.
One week, one week, one week, one week, one week, one week, one week, one week.
Again, question about those green boxes.
Yes.
And that was the most of the time.
On the side of the clock.
Because one is there instead of the little side of the clock.
I don't know if that's it.
It's something that we're going to talk about in my sector.
I don't know if you can hear it.
You can hear it.
So, there's anything else we can do about it.
So, there's nothing else I can do about it.
That's it.
And it's, you can from it.
I said it perspective.
It's right to come.
Our part.
And it's great.
It's a life-rear.
It's not a piece of art.
I just thought we actually didn't need to hurry up.
We didn't need to hurry up.
The setting.
What are some options for me?
You need to be patient.
What are those?
Something.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't think the thing is, I don't think that.
I don't think that.
I mean, I don't think that.
Okay.
We have that in close to the source that they need in the large.
You know, our institution.
Thank you.
And the next thing is we're going to notify from the RDA that, you know, with the reason
that they had to pay where it was natural gas prices, we're off the charts with, you
know, we had a rolling block out, that we currently have an BCA, which is the power of
artificial intelligence, which are just for what it cost me to get to the power as far as
a natural gas portion or for a lot of portion of the whole portion, which, you know, is
a total of the total amount of natural gas goes to, you know, the total of the total
of the total of the total of the total of the total of the total of the total of the total
of the total amount of tons.
So they're important, that they're looking at the sum.
They're going to have, they call it BCAX, which would be the BCA,
but it's made in order to store their store in the end.
So they're trying to, because whenever they're buying natural gas for $3.00 a month,
they're going to, and it will sort of have to their pay and over $1.00 a month, they will
And obviously, even though there are paths at all, to us because they have to let it turn to generate power.
So they are looking at a term, they are trying to figure out how on they want to go about the two years, four years, six years, they take that average out.
They try to let such a good jump jump jump jump.
And the city is trying to pass the jump jump.
And I think that's a good one.
But they also need to kind of wait and turn around.
And I don't know if we can't do it.
So we're back fast.
On DJA was higher, we used to throw one bill.
It was a bit close to zero down.
So we have a little bit like that.
We can check what we have there.
I'm going to do a lecture there.
We'll go back one.
So it'll be a little bit like that.
I don't want to do it.
I'm going to say that.
Yeah.
I think it was a bit like that.
One thing I think we're going to do, I want that.
I'm going to tell you how we're going to do a lot of things.
I'm going to be able to do a lot of things.
I have some education on my body.
I don't know.
I think it's quite a score.
I think it's a lot of areas.
I think that's about that.
The movement is that the area where you're going to play it ends up is on the right.
You need to be a little bit.
We start.
You need to be able to.
So this is our area.
But it's getting more of the end.
So it's not over.
It's a little bit of a nice there.
I'm going to give them off.
We need to reach out.
That's a question.
That's obviously going to start out.
This is going to start out in the hospital.
Just kind of like that.
They're going to start out.
They'll be able to do that.
But then we can.
We can.
So we're going to start out at the hotel.
Or say,
Okay.
That's it.
All right.
We're going to go.
Bye.